She breaks the quiet, that's my name.
A nervous laugh, a world of shame. It's Aubrey,
just the same as you, but spelled a different
way, it's true.
She doesn't flinch, she doesn't run.
This simple kindness has begun.
I have to tell her, I have to say the reason I was
named this way.
My mother's name is Obri too, it's something
that she thought to do.
It was a joke that just kind of stuck A name I
curse, my rotten luck A label that she put on me
That I was never meant to be But looking at her I
can see A chance to change my history
This is my chance, this is the day I'll be the one
to walk away From Aubrey and Lafayette The name
she used inside my head This is my first act of
defiance My declaration of alliance
It was a joke that just kind of stuck But now I'm
making my own luck I'm shedding skin I've worn
too long A place where I could not belong You can
call me Jordan
Yeah, you can call me Jordan From now on
Call me Jordan